{
    "id": "7228f6c58ba14d7487dec135efca4b4f",
    "title": "They, Them, Their, Theirs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It took ………………….. an hour to finish the work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e3dcf09c7e9d4518be96562398ccc2a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You solve our problems and I will solve ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af0b691b616c4f0c953b42c99bb79ab0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was upset with both of ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67eca22bec274befbb7e5c7df93ada6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you heard of ………………… ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "224a21b17da1412298f882bfcffe2358"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are ………………… coming with us?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a3cbdaaedaf496284db1e66b8a575cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was very kind of ……………………… to help the poor old widow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a79e3b7dca144f0a92970b6692fd5237"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you speak to ………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "be625ec62ec449fb8311533e878222fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did …………………. see you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93ccdfcfcd6a49ceb5abdb03f719de28"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have ………………… been invited?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "109841ebc4ea4581b1dd504234996c7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ask …………………. if they can help?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba217c61a07745bfa8c4add4fa8ab7e8"
        }
    ]
}